[theme music playing]
-There's a spy in Diego's camp?
-We're a political family.
We have been doing this for many years.
It doesn't matter who's up against the
Ardientes because we're gonna win.
[Senator Magno] I would love
to get to know
your other son better.
Well excuse me, Senator,
but he's not my son,
and I cannot believe that you're
even considering that bastard.
I'm giving you until tonight
to finish your job.
Or else, do you see that toilet?
That's the last thing you'll see before
you die, you piece of shit!
Miss Ivy.
Where can I find Jaguar?
At the old hideout in the town of Gulod.
[gunshot]
[Julio] I'm here! Face me.
[gunfire]
[Rufo] My boss promised
to send us more men.
People who can help us gain
more money and power.
-I need to meet him.
-In due time.
[Camia] Lily, Senator Magno chose Diego!
[Ivy] That's great news!
[Camia] Thanks for helping out
with Diego's campaign.
[Ivy] Where is he? Let me talk to him.
[Camia] He's not around…
[Emilia] Do you have an update on Camia?
[Ivy] Just now, someone called Emilia
while we were on the phone.
They planted a spy in your camp.
[Nimfa] Camia does have a backer.
It's not Ivy Aguas.
It's Camia's daughter, Lily Cruz!
You heard me! Lily Cruz is alive!
[Emilia] Lily Cruz is dead! She's dead!
[Camia] Emilia planted a spy in our camp.
And there's only one person I suspect.
[Diego] Is it Nimfa?
[Camia] Diego, we need to investigate her.
[Emilia] I'll find Lily Cruz
no matter where she's hiding.
[Nimfa] Here you go. You get extra pieces
as a sign of my gratitude
for defending me earlier.
Nimfa, I just noticed something.
It's like Miss Camia
doesn't like you that much.
I don't get it either.
It makes me feel sad.
Because no matter
how nice you are to a person,
when they have a bad impression of you,
there's nothing you can do.
Well, maybe Miss Camia is just being wary.
Actually, all of us who support
Diego are like that too.
Who knows?
Someone from the opposing party
might be spying on us.
We can't help but be really cautious.
But you know what?
Don't worry about that.
Let's just chill for now.
-Chill?
-Mm-hm. Chill.
Because it looks like
this will take a while.
Wait, let me order more. Miss?
Three more bottles of beer, please.
Give them all to this woman.
[chuckles]
-Let's just have a toast!
-All right.
[Ivy] Yes, I want to know
everything about Lily Cruz.
I want info immediately.
Do you understand? Thank you.
Are you sure you want
to help Mom with this?
Of course, Arnaldo.
I need to help my future mother-in-law.
You know what, hon?
To be honest, I think Lily Cruz is dead.
Because if she were alive…
why would she let her mother
expose herself, right?
Well, anyway… Hon, I just want to ask you.
Do you think Emilia really
trusts her spy on Diego's side?
I just want to know who her spy is.
I'm just curious, why are you
suddenly so interested?
I mean, clearly, it's not an issue.
Lily Cruz isn't coming out anyway.
Besides, we have a wedding
to prepare. Right?
Yeah.
Of course, Arnaldo.
But, hon, I haven't forgotten
about our wedding.
I just want to help Emilia with this
for your future political career.
I want to know that spy,
so I can confirm
if Lily Cruz really is alive.
Who knows? That spy could
just be stirring trouble.
That's all it is.
Here.
[Nimfa] Thank you, Mr. Marlon.
I think you're forgetting something.
Your number.
Let me see that.
I have to go.
Nimfa, wait! Hang on.
-Hey!
-Stop it! Leave me alone!
What the hell is your problem?!
-We were getting along well,
-Hey, Batch.
and then you slap me?! What did I do?!
-Hey, what's going on?!
-We were having fun!
Marlon, you're drunk. Here, take a seat.
I drank a little, but I'm sober!
-Go on, sit down.
-That woman has a problem!
[Diego] What happened?
-What happened?
-Ask her.
I didn't do anything wrong! Tell him!
-What did you do to her?
-I didn't do anything!
Nimfa! Just a minute. Stay here. Nimfa!
She's crazy!
Nimfa! Nimfa!
Nimfa, wait. Are you all right?
I didn't think he'd do that to me.
I was leaving, then he just
asked for my number.
Thank goodness you arrived, Diego!
He would've harassed me
if it weren't for you.
Marlon wouldn't do that, Nimfa.
But, you should go home.
I'll take you, come on.
-No, Diego. No.
-Nimfa…
-Stay with me.
-Nimfa.
Please don't leave me.
Stay here! Stay with me.
-Nimfa, I think you're drunk.
-Stay with me. Stay with me.
Nimfa, stop!
What?! Don't you want me?
All the other guys do.
-Nimfa…
-They want this. They want me.
They want me. [crying]
Diego! Diego! Diego!
Nimfa, stop!
You have to understand, Nimfa,
that I'm in love with someone else.
You have to stop.
You're only hurting yourself!
You bastard! You're a jerk! I hate you!
I did everything to make you mine!
I let her control me!
-Nimfa!
-I became a bad person!
-What?!
-I did everything!
What did you say?!
What do you mean, Nimfa? What do you mean?
What did you just say?
Diego.
Diego, I've loved you for so long.
What did you do, Nimfa?!
But, no matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't take your mind off Lily.
And now, she's back…
You still want her, don't you?
How long are you going
to act like an idiot?
How long do you plan
on being so stupid?! How long?
-Nimfa, that's enough!
-Let me go! Let me go!
-Stop! Stop!
-Get off me!
I'm taking you home.
No, let me go!
Nimfa, that's enough.
I'm taking you home. Let's go.
That's enough, okay? Let's go.
Don't touch me! Don't touch me.
[Nimfa crying]
Stop crying, we have to go.
Come on, let me take you home.
Go ahead. Be with her.
But, mark my words…
If you two end up together,
I'll make every second
of your life miserable!
[tense music playing]
Nimfa.
Nimfa!
-Nimfa, are you okay?
[soft instrumental playing]
[moans]
-Raul?
-Yeah?
My goodness. Why are you home so late?
You know what I just found out?
Lily Cruz is alive.
And I expected you to at least support me,
but where were you again?
-I'm sorry.
-Are you cheating on me again?
Did you go back to your old ways?
What? Answer me.
I'm not cheating on you.
Let's just sleep. Ouch!
What's happening to you?
-That hurt.
-What's wrong?
Is that a stab wound or a gunshot?
Who did this to you?
-This is nothing.
-Who did that?
I had an encounter with one of my clients.
We had a misunderstanding. The
bastard didn't want to pay me.
I went after him, and he opened fire.
But I settled everything.
We sent him to prison.
That bastard had no idea who I was.
-[Raul grunts]
-I'm sorry, Raul. I'm sorry.
-This isn't serious.
-Wait. Let me call a doctor,
just to make sure everything's
going to be okay. Hold on, okay?
[Raul groans]
Hello? Doc.
Why did Nimfa mention Lily?
[Camia] Lily confirmed
that Emilia planted a spy
in our camp.
And there's only one person I suspect.
-Is it Nimfa?
-I know she's your friend…
but I can't help
but feel suspicious of her.
I caught her going through my things.
She told me that she needs money
for her sick father.
[tense music playing]
-[phone rings]
-Wait, you go on ahead.
I need to answer this call.
[phone rings]
-Yes?
-Hello, Mister Fernan.
-How are you?
-I'm good.
[chuckles] Oh, yeah, Diego.
I'm sorry I couldn't help out
with your campaign.
My brother asked me to help
out with the sugar cane harvest.
He doesn't have enough people to help him.
Harvest?
Isn't that bad for your health?
Not at all! I still have
strong bones, you know.
Who told you I was sick?
Why do you sound so concerned?
Uh… No reason, Mr. Fernan.
Take care over there.
Okay, then.
Nimfa, what have you done?
It's Nimfa?
My suspicions were right.
She watches my mother's every move
and reports all your plans
to Emilia and the Ardientes.
The Ardientes get wind of
all your plans because of Nimfa.
Your friend's so sweet.
She deserves a loyalty award.
Ivy, I don't know how Nimfa
could do this to me, either.
They are evil. They try to buy
everyone with their money.
They'll do everything to hold on
to their power.
That's why we shouldn't allow them to win.
You need to mislead Emilia.
She can't discover your true identity.
And I will keep an eye on Nimfa.
Diego, I want you to be careful.
And thank you for all your help.
Ivy, you need to be careful.
-You should go.
-Take care.
Thank you.
-Emilia.
-Yes, Aunt Claire?
It's confirmed.
This check didn't come from Ivy Aguas.
Who gave it then?
From a small company based here
in Ardiente.
[screams]
Emilia, get it together.
I'm so sick of being patient
and following all their orders!
But this time around,
I'm gonna do it my way,
so I can end this damn charade!
So, what are you going to do?
Emilia?
Why the broken porcelain?
It's too early to throw things around.
Are you okay?
Hi, Mamita.
It's a good thing you're here.
I was supposed to drop by your house.
I came here because I received
an invitation
from Senator Olivarez.
Let's go to his birthday party.
We might be able to convince him
to endorse Arnaldo.
No. I don't want to.
I can't concentrate because of Lily Cruz.
That's why you have to keep your promise.
We're going to hunt Lily Cruz. Okay?
Sure.
It's a good thing you're an idiot, Emilia.
She's right in front of you, moron.
Thank you, Ivy.
[crowd murmuring]
[woman] Lily Cruz?
That's Camia Cruz's daughter.
The woman going against the Ardientes.
-I thought she was dead?
-She's still alive.
[woman 1] Haven't you heard?
Emilia's nabbing all the women
who are the same age as Lily Cruz.
-Help! Help us!
-Somebody help us!
What will you do to them?
Where are you taking them?
Ivy, relax. You know,
you should take a chill pill.
I won't do anything today
that you won't like.
[ominous music playing]
-Come with us.
-Where are you taking us?
-Please, no…
Where are you taking us?
Get in.
-Come with us.
-Who are you?
Who are you? Let me go, mister!
-Mister! Let go of me!
-Hey!
[man] What will Emilia do to them?
Let's just pray that Emilia
doesn't go completely insane.
She's acting like she's possessed.
-That's right.
-You need to be careful, okay?
-And you?
-Emilia's pure evil.
Right.
[goon] Stay there!
-Stay there!
-[women crying]
-Is that all of them?
-From two communities, ma'am.
We haven't gone to the town proper yet.
Emilia, why did you have
to take them here?
What are you going to do with them?
Ivy, just watch.
Emilia…
Why are you all crying?
I haven't done anything yet.
Well?
Stop crying!
Oh, girls, it's like
you don't know me at all.
I only brought you here because
I wanted us to chat a little.
So, how are you, friends?
Mrs. Emilia, why did you take us here?
What do you think?
Why would I bring you here?
Because you're looking for
Lily Cruz, Camia's daughter.
You're right. And why do
you think I'm looking for her?
Because you're afraid she might
file charges against you,
like what Camia did.
-Emilia, stop it?
-What did you say?!
-Emilia!
-What did you say?! Tell me!
Do I look afraid?!
-Emi--
-Stay there!
Stop it, please.
Next.
What's your name?
Evangeline Macaspac, ma'am.
How would I know
if you're telling the truth?
Or if that's just your alias?
What if you're Lily Cruz?
Mrs. Emilia, I'm not Lily Cruz.
I'm the daughter of Mando
and Linda Macaspac.
I'm a public school teacher.
I'm not Lily Cruz.
You talk too much! Stay back! Go!
You're all too loud!
Shut up! Come here. Now!
[women crying]
[Emilia] Stop crying.
You! What's your name?
Everyone, even though the senator's party
is helping us with the campaign,
I still want us to have
our own source of funds.
Let's organize dance and game festivals…
as well as weekend markets.
If you have other suggestions,
just tell Nimfa.
Nimfa. You'll be my assistant from now on.
What? All right. I would love to.
-Lucky you, Nimfa.
-[laughs]
Well, since you're his assistant now,
help me prepare some snacks for them.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Pandoy.
[tense music playing]
Batch. What was that?
You sided with her last night,
and now, you even made her your assistant?
I know you did nothing wrong, Batch.
I'm just doing this
to avoid any conflict here.
-That's just it.
-All right then.
[phone rings]
I'll just take this.
-Hello, Ivy.
-Are you at the headquarters?
Yes, why?
Emilia's looking for Lily Cruz.
She's scouring all of Ardiente
and abducting every woman of Lily's age.
-[Emilia] Next!
-She's going to…
your headquarters next.
Ivy, get out of there. It's too dangerous.
-I can't do that.
-[Emilia] Idiots!
-[Emilia] What's your name?
-I need to stay here…
-to know about Emilia's plans.
-[Emilia] What?!
Diego, I just have one favor to ask.
Please… keep my mother safe.
Don't worry, I'll take care of her.
[Emilia] Rose Ann? Get over there!
Diego.
What's wrong?
[Emilia] You! Come here. What's your name?
-Susanna.
-Next!
-Emilia, stop it. Enough.
-Please stop!
You, what's your name?
You idiot! Get lost.
-Come here!
-You! What's your name?
[tense music playing]
Mm.
Arnaldo, where's your mother?
I need to talk to her.
Mom and Ivy went hunting.
They're hunting Lily Cruz.
But I'm going to stop them
before things get worse.
No, no, no. I think your mom
is right this time.
Lily Cruz's resurgence will only
be like opening Pandora's box.
Dead witnesses, closed cases,
and people I had to get rid of
because they were in the way of our plans.
It's best that we deal
with this Lily Cruz fiasco
as soon as possible.
There!
Since you didn't get anything
from them, let them go.
Too soon, Ivy. Too soon.
And you.
I overlooked your failure to catch Jaguar.
And now you can't even
help your crazy wife.
And all the while I thought
you rekindled your love
for each other?
Or… are you just saying you love your wife
whenever it's convenient?
I really do love my wife, Papa.
But a problem came up
with the business I'm running.
I'm still taking care of it. I'm sorry.
I'm not your wife,
but I can smell
your mistress from miles away.
Raul, I know you're hiding something.
Don't wait for me to find out,
or you'll be sorry.
You and my daughter are made
for each other.
You're both sloppy.
Emilia, aren't you getting tired of this?
You're scaring
all these women for nothing!
-I know!
-Stop this nonsense!
I'm going to stop interrogating, okay?
But I can't leave a stone unturned.
Oh, there you go!
Good afternoon, Camia Cruz!
I am looking for…
You're going to kidnap the
women here to find Lily Cruz.
Yes, Emilia. I know all
about your dirty games.
What you're doing is against human rights!
But whatever you do,
you'll never find Lily here!
You know, I really enjoy
talking to this woman.
She's so feisty!
Maybe your daughter is just like you.
But why isn't she here? Is she scared?
It doesn't matter. Um, Lily! Yoo-hoo!
Yoo-hoo! Lily, I'm here! Lily, I'm here!
-Emilia…
-I'm going to get you!
This is frustrating.
Why won't you come out?
Okay, if you don't want to come out…
just watch this.
Get some popcorn, and enjoy the movie.
Boys! Now.
-Wait!
-Emilia!
[Camia] Hey!
-Emilia! You're going crazy!
-Am I, Camia?
Because as I understand it,
if a daughter sees her mother in danger,
she'll come out and save her, right?
So, I assume Lily will do the same.
Take her. Now.
-Emilia, please.
-You can't take Aunt Camia!
Ah.
Wait, did I just hear
you say "Aunt," Diego?
Diego! I turn away for a second, and now…
you're calling this woman
like she's a blood relative?
You ungrateful piece of crap.
Unbelievable. Get them!
-Brace yourselves!
-Try us! Try us!
[clamoring]
-Emilia, please stop this!
-[Camia] Hold on. Wait!
Emilia! Fine, Emilia.
Because I don't want
these people to get hurt,
I'll come with you.
But promise me that nothing bad
will happen to me,
because if you don't,
all these people are witnesses
to your barbarity towards me!
Okay, okay. Quit whining.
Come on. Let's go.
Emilia.
-Ma'am Camia!
-I'm gonna follow you.
Ma'am Camia.
[crowd murmuring]
[quietly] Mom.
[tense music playing]
Bodyguards, follow them! Nanny, Uncle.
-Wait.
-We're going after them.
[Loring] What? Diego!
Marlon, take charge here!
-I'll take care of this.
-I can do this.
-Take care, all right?
-Diego.
-Take care, Diego.
-Yes, take care.
Take care, Batch, okay? Take care.
Why is Emilia looking for Lily Cruz here?
And why bother? She's been dead for years!
Ma'am Camia's problems never seem to end!
Now, even Diego's involved.
I just hope this all ends soon.
Miss Loring, Mister Pandoy… Lily is alive!
And she's here somewhere.
-What?!
What are you talking about?
I didn't tell Mrs. Emilia anything!
What about Emilia?
[tense music playing]
Uh.
Oh. What are you staring at?!
-Papa!
-Yes?
Arnaldo! Look who we have here.
-What?
-Hon.
Hon.
Whoa! [chuckles]
Wow!
Now, this is a surprise!
Miss Camia Cruz…
To what do we owe this pleasure?
[tense music playing]
[guards] You aren't allowed in here.
Oh, I get it!
Emilia, you're using Miss Camia Cruz
to lure Lily Cruz into the lion's den.
Yes, Papa.
Very well, then.
Let me get the happy place ready.
Wait!
Emilia, have you forgotten
about the promise you made to the people.
You swore you wouldn't
lay a hand on Camia Cruz.
If you do, it'll hurt Arnaldo's campaign!
If I were you, I'd keep your promise.
You know, Ivy, sometimes
you can really be silly.
You still don't know the family
you're marrying into.
You don't know how ruthless we can be!
-No, let me go!
-You're not allowed in here.
[action music playing]
Hold them here!
Take her!
-Don't touch me.
-[Diego] Let her go!
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm here to talk to you.
So let's keep things civil.
Put down your guns.
Put your guns down.
Let's talk about this properly!
Put your guns down. Now!
Emilia.
Put it down.
Arnaldo, put the gun down.
I guess now that we put the guns away…
it's your turn to fulfill your promise.
Where's your daughter?
How'd you find out
my daughter's still alive?
It doesn't matter how I found out.
Answer my question.
Is Lily alive?! Where is she?!
Yes! Lily is alive!
That's what you want to hear, right?!
My daughter is alive!
[suspenseful music playing]
Well, if your daughter's alive,
where is she? Bring her to us.
Is she helping you with Diego's campaign?
Will she resurface?
Is she going to press charges?
And will you admit you had
my daughter killed
just like what you tried to do to me?
Will she resurface just as you did?
Okay. You know what? We don't need this.
We'll only have a harder time
with the election.
No, Arnaldo. I can eliminate the threat.
Are you trying to scare me, Emilia?
Camia. You're on our turf.
And I'm the one who calls the shots here.
And if you don't stick
to our agreement, Camia…
You heard about those women
I nabbed, right?
I'll kill them all, one by one.
Lily will not resurface.
I promise you that.
[Julio] Wait a minute.
How can we be sure that you're not lying?
If I don't follow the deal
you set, what will you do to me?
You'll have me killed?
You're going to stain your name
with me and my daughter's blood?
[scoffs] And during
election season, no less!
Not even the fortune of this
Ivy Aguas can save you.
Your family will be ruined, and
there's no way you'll recover.
Aunt Camia, how are you? Are you okay?
Diego, the Ardientes already
know that Lily is still alive.
I think… I think I need
to talk to my daughter.
WE NEED TO TALK. LET'S MEET.
Hon, I need to go.
But why?
If you need to rest, you can stay here.
I can rest better at home.
Okay, but I'll have the driver
take you home.
That won't be necessary, hon.
I'll just see you tomorrow, okay?
-Emilia, good night.
-Good night.
Congressman.
Good night, hon. I love you.
[Arnaldo] I love you too.
See you tomorrow.
Good night. See you tomorrow.
I'll just see her out.
-Okay.
-You're so sweet! Bye!
She's sweet tonight.
Romeo and Juliet!
[chuckles]
Ah!
I think I'm going to call it a night too.
Good night, earthlings!
Tomorrow's another day to catch
the traitors of this family.
I believe my daughter's
got all the bases covered?
Yes, Papa. You just wait and see.
Very good.
-Good night, Papa.
-Good night.
-Rest well.
-And you too.
[grunts]
[melancholic music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
I'm sure about this,
Ma'am Emilia. Lily's coming.
And I'll find out just who she is.
Take a video, and send it
to me immediately.
If you pull that off, you're free to go.
And I'll send the remaining
balance to you,
the house and lot as well.
Good job.
[quietly] Thank you. Thank you, ma'am.
Just a little bit more,
and I can finally make
my dreams come true.
Bye-bye.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
[muffled shriek]
[no audible dialogue]
Mom. I'm sorry that I had
to point a gun at you earlier.
It's all right, Lily. I understand why.
The survey results are about to come out.
We need to gain the public's sympathy.
That's why I took it upon myself
to find you an electoral party.
Here.
It's tonight.
It's Senator Olivares' birthday.
He's Senator Magno's rival.
Well, let me guess…
-You want me to charm this man.
-No.
I want something else to happen.
I want them to bend
over backward to make you
a part of their party.
It's different, right?
[pensive music playing]
Want some, hon?
Sure. Thank you.
Senator Carlito Olivares' birthday…
For Arnaldo?
No, thanks. [scoffs]
Ever since he became active
in human rights causes,
I stopped associating with him.
But, Papa, you and his father
used to belong to the same party.
And I remember having breakfast
with his dad when I was young.
His dad, yes. But Carlito? He's two-faced.
I don't want anything
to do with him, with his party,
whether political or otherwise.
Fine. I just thought it could help Arnaldo
if we attended as a complete family.
I'll think about it.
Anyway, how about you?
Have you fixed all your problems?
Is that why you're looking for
another endeavor to screw up?
I know Camia and Diego.
Knowing them, they're willing
to sacrifice their own agenda
for everyone's safety, Papa.
So, I believe they won't reveal Lily Cruz.
Well, not for now or in the near future.
I see.
How could you do this to us, Nimfa?
We were good to you!
How could you rat us out to Emilia?
Why did you let her use you?!
Because I'm sick of this life!
Why?
Can you give me what she promised?
You're only relying on your backer.
Diego is your friend.
You threw all that away.
For what?! For what, Nimfa?!
It's none of your business!
Why? Do you have any proof?
Just let me go.
There's no point to this!
I need to get my prize.
-Give it to me!
-Let go!
-Let go of me!
-I said give it to me!
-Auntie.
MA'AM E, I HEARD CAMIA
IS GOING TO MEET UP WITH LILY.
KEEP A CLOSE EYE ON CAMIA,
-AND TAKE A VIDEO OF THEM BOTH.
-OKAY, MA'AM E.
How dare you?!
[Nimfa grunting]
-Aunt Camia!
-Let go of me!
Auntie! Auntie!
How dare you?! You idiot! You liar!
[sobs]
Diego. Diego. Diego.
-Diego!
-Nimfa, how could you do this?
-Diego.
-What were you thinking?
-Diego, forgive…
-Why did you do that?!
Because I want to be like Ivy Aguas.
Emilia promised to give me a better life.
I was blinded by it because
I'm sick of being so poor!
I want to become rich, to have
a car and my own business.
Haven't you realized
that they're just using you?
There are other ways
to achieve your dreams.
You know Emilia and her family
are murderers and liars!
Diego, Emilia promised me
you'd be mine after all this.
Well, she lied to you!
I did all this hoping
I could make you love me, Diego!
But you only have eyes for Ivy… for Lily.
[Nimfa crying]
Black diamond?
Wait, I have to take off my earrings.
-It doesn't match the necklace.
-Mm-hm.
Thank you, but what is this for?
I just want to thank you
for helping me find Lily Cruz.
You know, I just appreciate your effort.
It's nothing. But, thank you.
It's beautiful.
You're welcome.
So, shall I see you at Senator
Olivares' party later?
Yes, of course. I'll see
you later. I have to go.
Wait, Ivy. I'm just curious.
How did you get an invite to the party?
It's simple. I am Ivy Aguas.
I own the top company here in
the country. So, I'm in demand.
Hmm.
That's why you even got Arnaldo
and our whole family invited.
But, do you even think
it's worth our attendance?
[scoffs]
I didn't do it for nothing.
Let's just say we're hitting
two birds with one stone.
And, yes, if we secure
Senator Olivares' endorsement
for Arnaldo's campaign then
it means, it's all worth it.
What about you, Emilia?
It seems like you didn't get an invite.
Hmm?
Me? What are you saying, Ivy?
I'm Emilia Ardiente,
the queen of Ardiente.
Of course, I have an invite! Come on.
Oh, right. You're in demand too.
You want to have this?
Aww. We're exchanging gifts now?
-Aww. Thank you.
-Why not?
-You're welcome.
-[giggles]
So sweet of my daughter-in-law.
And when Arnaldo and I get married,
I'll give you more than that.
Me too. I can give you more too.
I know.
We're exchanging gifts!
Aunt, here's the phone.
Diego.
We can't lock her up here forever.
I'll think of other plans for Nimfa.
But for now, we can't let her go
because I know
she'll go straight to Emilia.
She'll expose Ivy's identity.
But I know Nimfa's life is in danger too…
once Emilia finds out that
we already know their secret.
If we think about it, Nimfa's
a victim of the Ardientes too.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Marlon.
Do I really need to go there?
All right.
Auntie Camia, I have to go.
Please watch over Nimfa.
All right, I can manage here.
Take care, Diego.
Thank you, Auntie Camia.
Fundraising activities,
national games, Sunday market,
and public dance parties?
How do you expect to raise huge funds
if all you've got are small gimmicks?
Sir, with all due respect,
that's really Diego's branding.
-[Marlon] It courts the masses.
-But we need big ideas.
Tent-pole strategies!
Also, I brought in some new equipment.
It was a donation from the owner
of the largest mall chain in Manila.
Hold on. First of all,
Marlon's the campaign manager.
Secondly, you should inform me
each time you accept a donation.
Because the minute those people
ask me to return the favor,
I can't guarantee that I would.
Relax. I'm the representative
of the party.
And, my job is to ensure that your vision
is aligned with that of the party.
We still have a lot of things to do.
Let's plan our strategies well. Okay?
[Marlon] Okay.
Nimfa? Have something to eat.
No. I need to go home.
Where's my cellphone?
[pensive music playing]
You know, I understand
how you feel, Nimfa.
I also dreamt of having a better life,
and I'd also do anything
for the people I love.
So I understand
why you made that decision.
I know what you're doing.
You're being nice to me
so I won't push through with my plan.
[tense music playing]
I'm still telling Emilia about
the information I discovered!
Now, where's my phone?!
Diego said that we shouldn't let you leave
because he's afraid
of what Emilia could do to you.
Besides, even after
everything you did to us,
we still consider you part of this family.
[sighs]
And we love you.
[tense music playing]
You're a good actress, Camia.
But you still can't fool me.
Get out of my way!
Hey! Stay here!
We're not letting you leave
because we care about you!
Do you understand?!
We're good people, Nimfa!
That's right. You really had me fooled!
-[woman shouts indistinctly]
-Nimfa!
Ivy, it's Nimfa.
She's the one who told Emilia
that Lily is still alive.
[Ivy] Arnaldo.
-Arnaldo.
-Hon, I can explain.
-[grunts]
-Arnaldo!
If you think I'm betraying you,
then I guess, Arnaldo,
we should call off our wedding.
-After her!
-Ma'am Emilia.
So you're Mom's spy.
I need to tell her something
about Miss Ivy.
She's the one feeding…
-information to Diego's camp!
-That's not true!
You need to know that Ivy is--
-[gunshots]
[theme music playing]